HARZALLAH Mohamed Amine

I am a student in the 3rd year of engineering ,specializing in Computer Science at Polytechnic Private University of Sousse. The university is labeled CTI and EUR-ACE. My specialization is in software engineering with a focus on Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Big Data.

Work Experience_____

End-of-Studies Internship: Leoni [February 2024 - Present]

Engineer internship: Leoni [June 2023 - July 2023](2months)

Internship SmartLogger [october 2022 - February 2023](5 months)

Creation of a mobile application (Flutter, Nodes, mongoose).

Technical Internship *SmartLogger* [July 2022 - August 2022](1month)

Creation of a website application (ReactJs, NodeJS)

Worker Internship *MakerLab* [June 2022 - July 2022](1month)

Creation of dynamic website application (Laravel, Livewire).

Technical Internship *TMN Startup* [December 2021 - March 2022](4months)

Creation of dynamic website application (Front-End) (ReactJs).

Technical Internship *MakerLab* [July 2021 - August 2021](2months)

Creation of dynamic website application (HTML,CSS,JS,PHP,MYSQL).

Projets_

The Prediction of plant disease (potatoes,tomato,pepper) Python(machine Learning)

The detection of fake news (NLP)

Python(machineLearning)

Data processing & Power BI Big Data

HDFS,MapReduce , cleaning Data using Talend,Data

Warehouse Data Visualisation using Power BI

Car Price Prediction & data processing

Python(machine Learning), cleaning data, Power BI

Management of a fitness center React.js,

,SpringBoot ,Postgresql

Invoice Management React.js, ,expressJs,MongoDB

Devops *Jenkins,Kubernetes*

Skills

- Artificial Intelligence: Python (machine learning)
- Framework: Flutter ,Spring Boot,Flask .
- Library: ReactJS, Flowbite, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap
- Development platform:NodeJs
- Programming languages: C,Python,HTML,CSS,JS,PHP,SQL,JAVA
- Database :Postgresql(SQL),MongoDB(NOSQL)
- Dev–IDE Platforms: Visual Studio, Android Studio, Pycharm
- Operating systems: Linux, Windows
- Modeling language: UML

Education

- [2021 Present] : Engineering diploma in Computer science.: Polytechnic Private University of Sousse(EUR-ACE,CTI)
- [2020 2021]: 1st year Industrial Electronics: National Engineering School of Sousse.
- [2018-2020]: Preparatory Diploma Physics-Chemistry sector : Preparatory institute for engineering studies Monastir
- [2017-2018]: University Reorientation Entrance Exam for Medical.
- [2017]: Bachelor of Experimental Science, Fattouma Bourguiba High school.

Certification

- IT Specialist Python
- AI-900: Microsoft Azure AI Fundamentals
- DELF B2
- CCNA I
- CCNA II
- Participation in the competition the night IT 2021 and 2022
- Participation in the IA challenge 2023 competition(arsii)

Language_____

- French
- English
- Germany(Beginner)
- Arabic